Welcome back to a new video, guys. As
欢迎回到新视频，朋友们。
you can see, there's nothing in my
如你所见，我的冰箱里空荡荡的，冰箱里也几乎没什么东西。
freezer and almost nothing in my fridge.
这意味着我们需要去超市购物。加入我。
That means we need to go do some
我们的清单是柑橘类水果。上次在这里吃熟鱼是什么时候？
shopping at the grocery store. Join me.
酒吧被称为包装商品来自许多液体。堆放开放。
Our list citrus. When's the last place
味道开始计数，让我们出发。
at any cooked fish here? Bar called
好了，朋友们，我们到了市场。
packaged goods from many liquid
海鲜、家禽、肉类、蔬菜、鲜花和香料。我们走吧。
compostables. Tour open stocking up.
看起来不大，但还挺好看的。
Taste of start the word count and let's
这个不大。这是那个。那个不大。
go. Okay guys, we're at the market.
你要篮子吗？
Seafood, poultry, meat, vegetables,
我们推购物车吧。
flowers, and spices. Let's go.
里面很冷。
>> Doesn't look that big, but it looks kind
是啊，我知道。感觉满了。我们就推个购物车吧。
of nice.
你要这么多东西吗？
>> This one isn't that big. This is the
不需要，但我们还是推个购物车吧。
ger. The ger isn't that big.
好的，所以我们推购物车。
>> You want a basket?
You want a basket?
>> Let's get a cart.
Let's get a cart.
>> It was cold in there.
It was cold in there.
>> Yeah, I know. It feels full. Let's just
Yeah, I know. It feels full. Let's just
take a shopping cart.
>> You want that much stuff?
You want that much stuff?
>> No, but we'll just grab a shopping cart.
No, but we'll just grab a shopping cart.
Okay, so we're getting a shopping cart.
We don't really need that much stuff,
我们真的不需要那么多东西，
but uh might as well.
但嗯，也行。
>> Yeah. I mean, no.
是啊。我的意思是，不是。
>> Oh, but it's cold in here.
哦，但这里很冷。
>> Oh.
哦。
>> Oh, man. It's actually pretty small.
哦，天哪。其实还挺小的。
>> Yeah.
是啊。
>> Okay. So, let me pull out the list.
好的。那么，让我拿出清单。
Okay. So, this is our list. Toilet
好的。那么，这是我们的清单。卫生纸
paper, bags, toothpaste, soap,
垃圾袋，牙膏，肥皂，
detergent, and large water bottles.
洗涤剂，和大的水瓶。
>> We have bags, though.
但我们有垃圾袋啊。
>> Do we?
我们有吗？
>> I have that roll that we bought in South
我有我们在韩国买的那卷。
Korea.
哦，是真的。所以没有垃圾袋。那么，我们
>> Oh, that's true. So, no bags. So, we do
不需要垃圾袋了。卫生纸，牙膏，肥皂，洗涤剂，水瓶，
not need bags anymore. Toilet paper,
和嗯，汽水。看看这里有多少种不同的根茎。
toothpaste, soap, detergent, water
这看起来像瓜，对吧？但它不是。
bottles, and uh soda. Look at all these
是啊。那是酸橙。
different roots here.
这是你可以买到的最大柑橘类水果。
>> This looks like a melon, doesn't it? But
This looks like a melon, doesn't it? But
it's not.
>> Yeah. That's a sweet sour pomelo.
Yeah. That's a sweet sour pomelo.
>> This is the biggest citrus fruit you can
This is the biggest citrus fruit you can
buy.
>> Really?
真的吗？
>> Yeah. It's like a giant orange.
是啊。像个大橙子。
>> Wow. Citrus fruit.
哇。柑橘类水果。
>> And the skin on this is like an inch
而这颗的皮有1英寸厚。
thick.
真的吗？但这里按公斤计价。
>> Really? But you're paying for kilograms
正是。
here.
所以你基本上是在买皮。
>> Exactly.
比较是。
>> So you're kind of paying for skin
但你也可以用这皮来做糖果之类的，如果你想要的话。
>> pretty much. But you can use the skin
是啊。所以这里像是生鲜区。这里还有更多水果。
too to make like candy and stuff if you
有香蕉。要买些香蕉吗？
want.
是啊，我们可以买些香蕉。
>> Yeah. So this is like the produce
好吧，那我们去拿些香蕉吧。
section. There are more fruits here.
你上次吃香蕉是什么时候？
There are bananas. You want to get some
呃，昨天。
bananas?
真的吗？
>> Yeah, we can get some bananas.
香蕉糖。
>> Well, let's grab some bananas then.
所以，我就拿了这包。现在，我们要去选些香蕉。哪个
When's the last time you even had any
bananas?
>> Uh, yesterday.
Uh, yesterday.
>> Really?
Really?
>> A banana candy.
A banana candy.
>> So, I just grabbed this uh bag. Now,
So, I just grabbed this uh bag. Now,
we're going to pick some bananas. Which
ones look good?
这看起来怎么样？
>> Maybe this one right here.
可能就是这个。
>> This one?
这个？
>> Yeah.
对。
>> Now, I'm going to put the bananas in the
现在，我要把香蕉放进
bag.
袋子里。
Bananas are now in the bag. And I'm
香蕉现在在袋子里了。我将
going to place it into my shopping cart.
它放到购物车里。
If you want to get my 3,000 most common
如果你想获得我整理的3,000
English words PDF to help you understand
个最常见英语单词PDF，帮助你
up to 95% of spoken English with real
理解95%的英语口语，里面
clear definitions and examples organized
包含真实、清晰的定义和例句，
by suffer level and topic, then check
按难度等级和主题分类，可以
out the link in my description to get
点击我描述中的链接获取。
it. What were you saying?
你刚才说什么？
>> I was going to say that this one does
我想说这个看起来不太好看，
not look that good cuz it has
因为它已经熟过头了。
>> Yeah, it's starting to uh ripen too
对，它熟得太快了。如果熟
much. If it ripens too much, it becomes
过头，就会变褐变黑。哥们，我
like brown and then black. Dude, I've
从没见过这么多水果。
never seen a lot of these fruits.
这是个柑橘类水果，我想。
>> This is a citrus, I think. Yeah. Look,
对。看，这也是个柚子。
this is also a pomelo.
哦，哥们，这太大了。
>> Oh, dude, that's huge.
它们变得非常巨大。但你得
>> They get really massive. But you got to
remember the skin is thick.
记得要脸皮厚点。
>> Yeah. And this is the vegetable area.
嗯。这里都是蔬菜区。
So, there are a lot of vegetables here.
所以，这里有很多蔬菜。
>> Are you planning to do much cooking?
你打算做很多烹饪吗？
>> No. That's why I just bought bananas and
不。这就是为什么我只买了香蕉和
the rest of the stuff on my list. The
列表上的其他东西。列表上的
rest of the stuff, toilet paper,
其他东西，卫生纸、牙膏、肥皂，
toothpaste, soap, none of these are
这些都不是烹饪原料。所以，我不会
ingredients for cooking. So, I won't be
做任何烹饪，但让我们把香蕉
doing any cooking, but let's add banana
加入列表。
to the list.
你知道，我们在中文杂货店
>> You know, we're in a Chinese grocery
的时候有糯米团子。
when you have gluten balls.
嘿，你看那些。看看那些辣椒的
>> And dude, look at those. Look at the
大小。
size of those peppers.
但我可以保证那些不是很辣。
>> But I can guarantee that those are not
好的，我们去拿卫生纸
very spicy.
牙膏。我们必须离开蔬菜区。
>> Okay, let's get the toilet paper
这里是鱼类区。
toothpaste. We have to go outside of the
这里有很多鱼。
produce area. Here is the fish area.
这个看起来像食人鱼。
There are a bunch of fish here.
像食人鱼。是的，那些看起来像
>> This almost looks like a piranha.
那种。
>> Like a piranha. Yeah, those look like
那些是鲷鱼。
kind of like
>> those are mac.
those are mac.
>> Yeah. Let's go around this area. There
是的。我们去绕这个区域看看。
is just a lot more produce. And right
这里的农产品种类更多。
now I'm pushing the shopping cart
现在我正推着购物车穿过超市。
through the grocery store. And I guess
我猜这里就是结账的地方。不，那是
this is where you pay. Or no, that's
称重的地方。
where you weigh your goods.
哦，可能得在那里称重。
>> Oh, maybe you got to weigh there.
是的。你想称这些香蕉吗？
>> Yeah. Do you want to go weigh these
好的，我来称。
bananas?
我去那边。是的，Leon
>> Yeah, I'll weigh them.
正在称香蕉。
>> I'll go to the side here. So yeah, Leon
他说什么？
is just weighing the banana.
他在指那个方向。
>> What'd he say?
好的，那是一个水果称重站。
>> He's pointing me that way.
所以Leon需要先去称他的水果。
>> Okay, so that is a fruit weighing
通常在加拿大是在结账时称重，但
station. So Leon needs to first go and
这里看起来是在这里称。
weigh his fruit. Usually in Canada they
谢了，兄弟。420。
do this when you get to the cash
那相当于A150
register, but here it looks like they do
加拿大币。所以他们在水果称重站称
it here.
我们的香蕉，然后贴上价格标签。
>> Thank you, bro. 420.
所以当我们去
>> That's like uh A150
That's like uh A150
>> Canadian. So they weigh our bananas at
Canadian. So they weigh our bananas at
the fruit weighing station and then put
a price tag on it. So when we go to
check out, they'll scan this barcode.
查一下，他们会扫描这个条形码。
And I guess that one was the vegetable
我猜那个是蔬菜区。
area.
是的，我觉得他们标志上写着
>> Yeah, I think they the signs say
也是蔬菜。
vegetable, too. Here we have some uh
这里有一些冷冻肉类。看起来是。
frozen meats. Looks like Yeah. Beef
牛肉。哦，他们有巴西牛肉。如果你
feet. Oh, they have Brazilian beef. Let
来自巴西，请告诉我。这边他们
me know if you're from Brazil. Over here
有羊肉。你觉得我们应该买些调味品
they have mutton. Do you think we should
比如番茄酱或者烧烤酱之类的吗？
buy like condiments like ketchup or
是的，我觉得番茄酱不错。
barbecue sauce or something?
我也这么认为。哦，鸡蛋。你觉得
>> Yeah, I think ketchup would be good.
我们应该买些鸡蛋吗？
>> I think so. Oh, eggs. You think we
是的，还不错。一包11个。11
should buy some eggs?
是什么？
>> Yeah, they're not bad. 11 per packet. 11
11大概4美元。
is what?
是的。
>> 11 is like $4.
我们要买吗？
>> Yeah.
是的，这些看起来很受欢迎。我们就
>> Should we buy?
买这些吧。是的，我觉得可以选这个。
>> Yeah, these ones look popular. We'll
那么，这些有多少个？
just get these ones. Yeah, I guess we
两打。哦，30个。
could go with that one. So, how many are
30个鸡蛋。现在我要拿
these?
>> Two dozen. Oh, 30.
Two dozen. Oh, 30.
>> 30 eggs. Now, I'm going to take the
30 eggs. Now, I'm going to take the
carton of eggs and place it into the
一箱鸡蛋，然后把它放进购物车里
shopping cart. I've just placed the eggs
我刚刚把鸡蛋放进购物车里了
into the shopping cart. Here we have
我们现在有包装商品
packaged goods. A lot of packaged goods.
很多包装商品
I think we've added more things that
我想我们添加的购物清单以外的商品
aren't from our list than from our
比清单上的商品还多
actual list. Toothpaste, soap,
牙膏、肥皂
detergent, toilet paper, water, and
洗涤剂、卫生纸、水
soda. Oh, water is over here. Should we
和汽水
just buy a big water and then we could
哦，水在这里。我们应该
refill it at the Or should we buy like
直接买大瓶水，然后可以在
something like this? No,
奥莱尔补充吗？或者
>> let's just take a big one.
我们应该买像这样的？
>> Or actually, I think this would be a
不，
better deal.
我们就买大瓶的吧。
>> You have to get natural mineral water.
其实，我觉得这个更划算。
That's what you want to look for.
你必须买天然矿泉水。
>> It's the same brand, Desel.
那就是你要找的。
>> But we have to carry this all the way
是同一个品牌，Desel。
back.
但我们必须把它们全部带回去。
>> That's true.
那是事实。
>> It's lowkey kind of heavy.
它有点重。
>> Maybe we'll get a grab then.
也许我们随便抓几个。
>> Okay, so we got our drinking water
好的，我们拿到了饮用水。
there. I think we'll probably have to
我想我们可能还需要
take a taxi back since that's going to
打出租车回去，因为那会非常重。应该不会太重。不。
be really heavy. It shouldn't be too
皮卡里汗。皮卡里汗从哪里来？
much. No.
日本。
>> Picari sweat. Where is Picari sweat
哦，是吗？
from?
是的。
>> Japan.
我第一次看到它是在韩国，所以我以为它是韩国的。汽水应该就在这附近。
>> Oh, is it?
对，就在这里。
>> Yeah.
但嗯，我觉得罐装的好。
>> First time I saw it, I saw it in Korea,
或者你想那些小瓶子？
so I thought it was Korean. Soda should
你可以买一大瓶汽水，一升半，但我觉得我们不可能一次喝这么多汽水。所以，我觉得买罐装的好。
be around here somewhere.
那是唯一一包。其他的都是单独包装的。哦，他们上面还有更多包，但都是一样的。是啊，那些是一包四瓶。
>> Yeah, right here.
哦，
>> But uh yeah, I guess cans are all right.
我猜我们拿那些吧。或者
Or do you want like those small bottles?
You could buy like a big thing of soda,
a liter and a half, but I don't think
we'll drink this much soda in one
sitting. So, I think the cans would be
better to buy.
>> That's the only packet. Everything else
That's the only packet. Everything else
is individual. Oh, they got more packets
up here, but it's the same. Yeah, those
comes in packets of four.
>> Oh,
Oh,
>> I guess let's get those. Or
I guess let's get those. Or
>> what about up there?
那上面怎么样？
>> Yeah, they have more sodas on the top
对，上面有更多的汽水
shelf. And there are many shelves here.
架子。这里有很多架子。
And all these shelves are filled with
而且，这些架子都装满了
sodas.
汽水。
>> Carbonated yogurt drink like that. Uh
像那种碳酸酸奶饮料。呃
>> Milkus. Okay, let's uh just get this
奶露。好吧，那我们就先拿这个
then. Zero sugar. How many?
吧。零糖的。有多少？
>> I probably won't drink that. You can
我可能不会喝那个。你可以
have them.
拿它们。
>> Okay, so we just grabbed the soda. We
好的，那我们就先拿了汽水。我们
got eight cans here. Yeah, that should
这里拿了八罐。对，这样汽水就
be good in terms of soda. Should we grab
足够了。要不要拿个大瓶子的？是
a big one? is how much how many liters.
多少升？
Okay, so we're just going to grab these
好的，那我们就拿这几个
instead. The large bottles. We'll grab
吧。大瓶子。我们拿两个。不过
two. They don't have zero sugar though,
没有零糖的，不过，然后我们可以拿
but And then we can grab an A&W. So
个A&W。所以这样我们拿了三瓶汽水。那
there we got three soda. So we can check
我们可以把这个从清单上划掉了。我想
that off the list. I think the detergent
洗涤剂应该在那里。就在这个货架
will be there. It's on this aisle here.
上。
>> Okay. So I think we're going to get a
好的。所以我想我们要买液态
liquid detergent since we don't see any
洗涤剂，因为我们没看到任何洗衣
pods. So we're going to get this liquid
粒。所以我们要买这个液态洗涤剂
detergent for our washing machine. I
给我们的洗衣机。我
think all we need is one of these bags.
我们只需要一个这样的包。
We don't need a solid container.
我们不需要一个实心的容器。
>> Yeah, this will work for us.
嗯，这个适合我们。
>> Okay, perfect. There is also powder.
好的，完美。还有粉末。
Washing powder. Powder. But uh sometimes
洗衣粉。粉末。但是呢
powder leaves stains on your clothes, so
粉末有时会在衣服上留下污渍，所以
that's why I prefer to use liquid. We
那是我更喜欢用液体的原因。我们
can check that off the list. Detergent.
可以把这个划掉。洗涤剂。
Okay, guys. We finished doing all our
好了，各位。我们已经完成了所有
shopping. We got a 12-pack of water, but
购物。我们买了12瓶水，但是
each bottle is 1 and 1/2 L. We also got
每瓶是1又1/2升。我们还买了
three bottles of soda. I got toothpaste
三瓶汽水。我买了牙膏
cuz I need it. And uh we also got
因为需要。而且呢我们还买了
laundry detergent and some eggs and some
洗衣粉和一些鸡蛋和一些
bananas. So, we managed to get almost
香蕉。所以，我们基本上拿到了
everything. What's the two things we
几乎所有东西。我们没能买到哪
couldn't get?
两样东西？
>> Well, they did have toilet paper, but we
嗯，他们确实有卫生纸，但是
don't need a 12-pack. That's way too
我们不需要12包。那每个月
much toilet paper per month.
用这么多卫生纸太多了。
>> Yeah, we need like half of that. We just
嗯，我们只需要大概一半。
need six.
我们只需要六包。
>> Maybe a six-pack. Uh and then we also
也许六包就行。嗯，然后我们
need a bar of soap. I don't know why
还需要一块肥皂。我不知道他们
they didn't sell it here, but we'll go
为什么不卖，但是我们会去
to Watson's for that.
要去华生买那个。
>> Yeah, we need a bar of soap. I like
是的，我们需要一块肥皂。我喜欢
using a bar of soap to either wash my
用一块肥皂来洗我的手
hands or to lather up my hands to wash
或者搓手来洗身体
my body or to lather up my washcloth. So
或者搓洗抹布。所以
yeah, this is all the stuff we bought.
是的，这是我们买的所有东西。
And now we're waiting for our taxi.
现在我们在等出租车。
Yeah, we booked a Grab and now we're
是的，我们订了Grab，现在我们
just waiting for it to come. It's 5
正在等它来。现在还有5
minutes away now. So he should be here
分钟路程。所以他应该很快就到
soon and then he'll bring us to where
然后会带我们去住的地方。通常我们
we're staying. Normally we could just
可以直接走回去，但这太重了，要
walk back, but this is way too heavy to
搬超过一公里。我的意思是，我们
carry for over a kilometer. I mean, we
可能能做到，但只是坐出租车更方便。我们
could probably do it, but it's just more
在电梯里。我买了购物的东西。Leon
convenient to just get a taxi. We're in
拿着鸡蛋和水。我差不多已经
the elevator. I got the shopping. Leon
开始拆东西了。但我们买了牙膏，一
has the eggs and water. I kind of
捆水。我们把鸡蛋放这里。我还
started unpacking the stuff already. But
把汽水放冰箱里，因为呃，我不想
yeah, we got the toothpaste, bunch of
让它在外面。但这些袋子感觉像
water. We put the eggs here. And I
感觉一下。告诉我那感觉不一样。
already put the soda in the fridge just
because uh I didn't want it out. But
these bags feel like Feel that. Tell me
that does not feel different.
>> Yeah, I know. These aren't like regular
嗯，我知道。这些不是普通的购物袋，但这些是回收的。
shopping bags, but these are recycled.
就是这个原因。
That's why.
回收的。
>> Recycled.
它们是100%回收的。这就是为什么它们
>> They're 100% recycled. This is why they
感觉这样。它们是100%
feel like this. They're 100%
可堆肥的。哇。
compostable. here. Wow.
哦，我不是塑料袋。我是100%
>> Oh, I'm not a plastic bag. I'm 100%
可堆肥的。这是可生物降解的。所以，
compostable. This is biodegradable. So,
你可以留下这个，最终它会
you can leave this and eventually it'll
就，你知道，降解，而塑料则
just, you know, degrade compared to
像永远不会分解。所以，
plastic which like never decomposes. So,
如果你只是留下这个，它最终会
if you just leave this, it'll decompose
分解。但普通塑料不会
eventually. But regular plastic wouldn't
分解。它会啊，像存在成千上万年。
decompose. It would uh stay as plastic
哇。
for, I don't know, thousand years.
像塑料存在那么久。这就是为什么
>> Wow.
它感觉这么不同，因为我，我觉得，
>> However long plastic lasts. That's why
这感觉真的很不一样。它不像塑料。
it feels so different cuz I I was like,
嗯。我想这就是原因
this feels really different. It doesn't
我觉得在马来西亚他们更环保意识
feel like plastic.
因为即使吸管这些东西，它们还是
>> Yeah. And I guess that's why
在上面。
>> I think they're more environmentally
I think they're more environmentally
conscious in Malaysia cuz even the
straws and stuff, they're still on the
paper straws everywhere you go. And now
到处都是纸吸管。而现在
the fully compostable bags.
是完全可堆肥的袋子。
>> Yeah, that's cool. Guess we'll just
是啊，挺酷的。我们只好
throw these away. I don't really know if
扔掉这些了。我不太清楚
we have any use for them, but uh yeah,
我们还有什么用，但嗯，是的，
besides that, we just have a bunch of
除了这个，我们只是有一大堆
water. Let's just uh put this in the
水。我们就把它放冰箱里吧。
fridge. Eh,
呃，
>> yeah, might as well.
那还不如。
>> So Leon just tore open this water bottle
所以Leon把这里的塑料水瓶
plastic here, and now he's putting them
撕开了，现在他正把它们
in the fridge. all the water bottles.
放进冰箱。所有的水瓶。
So, we got a lot of water here. How long
所以这里有很多水。你觉得
do you think this will last?
这能撑多久？
>> Uh I mean, I usually drink one a day.
嗯，我通常一天喝一瓶。
So,
所以，
>> okay, we'll divide it in half and then
好的，我们分成两份，然后
if these are up, you're going to have to
如果这些用完了，你就得
go and fill these up cuz we do have a
去装满这些，因为我们确实有
area to fill up the water bottles up a
地方可以装满水瓶，在几层楼。
couple floors. So, we don't necessarily
所以，我们不一定需要
need to go buy more. We can just go
去买更多的。我们只需要
upstairs and refill these.
上楼去重新装满这些。
>> Imagine if these waters tasted like Dani
想象一下如果这些水尝起来像
cuz we haven't tried this one yet.
Dani，因为我们还没试过这个。
Yeah, that would suck. But honestly, as
嗯，那会很难受。但说实话，只要水是冷的，就还好。
long as water's cold, it's not that bad.
所以，现在我要把这个瓶子递给Leon。我也会把这个给Leon。
So, now I'm going to pass this bottle to
还有最后两个。
Leon. I'll pass this one to Leon as
好了。扔掉吧。我们稍后会扔掉。
well.
这是我们放鞋的地方。鞋子不太整齐，但也不算乱。
And then the last two.
嗯，这就是我们的公寓。
There you go. Throw that away. We'll
那边是我的房间。Leon的房间在那边。Leon的浴室在这里。
throw that out later. This is where we
我的浴室在房间里。这里是我们客厅。我们有电视，这是我们餐桌。
put our shoes. The shoes aren't really
所以，这就是我们吃饭的地方。这是我们厨房区域，我们会在这里做很多饭。
organized, but it's not that messy
呃，太多了。哦，我们没买鸡蛋用的油或黄油。
either. But yeah, this is our apartment.
哦，对。我都不知道这里有什么锅具之类的。
That's my room over there. Leon's room
我想我们只能把鸡蛋煮了。
is over there. Leon's washroom's here.
那也行。
And my washroom is inside the room. This
right here is our living room. We have a
TV and this is our dining table. So,
this is where we'll eat. And this is our
kitchen area where we will be doing a
lot of cooking. Eh, so much. Oh, we
didn't buy oil or butter for the eggs.
>> Oh, that's right. I don't even know what
Oh, that's right. I don't even know what
kind of pans and stuff we have here.
>> I guess we'll just have to boil the
I guess we'll just have to boil the
eggs.
>> That's fine, too.
That's fine, too.
>> And eat boiled eggs.
然后吃煮鸡蛋。
>> Do we even have salt and pepper?
我们甚至有盐和胡椒吗？
>> No idea. Oh, but we have a lot of
不知道。哦，不过我们这里有很多
utensils here. So, okay guys, so Leon
用具。所以，好吧各位，所以Leon
asked me if this water tastes like Dani.
问我这水是不是Dani牌的。
This water brand is Desa, but uh there
这个水品牌是Desa，但是呃北美洲
is a water brand in North America called
有一个叫Dani的水品牌，那是史上最差的水。
Dani, which is the worst water ever.
它属于可口可乐公司，但是Dani，没人买那个。
It's owned by uh the Coca-Cola company,
最近美国经历了一场大雪暴，我在Tik Tok上
but Dani, no one buys that. Recently
看到视频里超市完全空了，因为人们
there was a there was a big snowstorm
在囤积各种商品和必需品，这样他们
that went through America and I saw
就能在大雪暴期间不用担心物资问题。然后
videos on Tik Tok of like grocery stores
他们展示了水区，唯一没人买的水品牌是
completely empty because people were
Dani。整排货架都清空了。水区没有
stocking up on different products and
其他水品牌，因为所有人都把它们买完了。
different uh essentials so that they
其他所有品牌在这个超市都卖完了。唯一
could wait out the snowstorm without
worrying about supplies. And then they
were showing the water section and the
only water brand that no one bought was
Dani. The whole aisle was cleared. There
were no other water brands on the water
aisle because everyone bought them all.
All the other brands were sold out at
this particular grocery store. The only
brand that was still full was Dani. That
那个仍然很满的品牌是Dani。那
just shows you how much people hate
就证明了人们有多讨厌
Dani. They really do not like the taste
Dani。他们真的不喜欢Dani的味道
of Dani. And I agree. Dani tastes like
。我也同意。Dani吃起来像
chlorinated water. It tastes terrible.
氯水。味道太差了。
It tastes like you took a bottle and you
它吃起来就像你拿一瓶子
went to your pool and you filled it up
去你的游泳池，装满水
with water and then you just started
然后就开始喝，突然这
drinking that and all of a sudden this
视频就变成了我吐槽Dani。
video is turning into like me roasting
但我只是告诉大家事实。Dani在北
Dani. But I'm just telling you guys the
美洲不好喝。但我们之前在
facts. Dani does not taste good in North
马来西亚有Dani，其实不
America. But here we had Dani in
坏。它和北美洲的Dani完全
Malaysia and it wasn't that bad
不同，显然是因为他们有不同
actually. It tasted completely different
的灌装设施。所以，水不来自
than the Dani in North America obviously
同一个地方。这就是为什么它
because they have different bottling
味道不同。总之，我试过这
facilities. So, the water doesn't come
种水。让我再试一次给你们看。
from the same place. That's why it
实际上还行。它有点点甜，
probably tastes different. Anyways, I
但除此之外，味道很棒。
tried this water. Let me try it again
for you guys.
It's actually not bad. It kind of has
like a little little bit of sweetness to
it, but besides that, it tastes great
and it's warm. Usually, warm water
而且它很暖。通常，温水
doesn't taste as good, but this water
的味道没有那么好，但这水
tastes perfectly fine. Nothing wrong
味道完全没问题。没什么不对
with it. But yeah, I just wanted to give
的。不过，是的，我只是想给
you guys that history and little bit of
你们讲讲这段历史和关于
uh information on Dani. The other thing
丹尼的一些信息。我还注意到
I noticed is that these bananas, this
的是这些香蕉，这一串香蕉
bunch of bananas look completely
看起来和我们在北美得到的
different than the bananas that we get
香蕉完全不同。在加拿大和美国，
in North America. In Canada and the
我们只有卡文迪什香蕉。我相信
United States, we only get Cavendish
它们被称为卡文迪什香蕉。嘿，利昂，
bananas. I believe they are called
加拿大的香蕉叫什么名字？
Caendish bananas. Yo, Leon, what are the
卡文迪什香蕉，对吧？
bananas we get in Canada called?
是的。
Cavendish bananas, eh?
是的。是的。所以，它们被称为
>> Yeah.
卡文迪什香蕉。这些香蕉肯定
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, they are called
不是卡文迪什香蕉。我不知道
Cavendish bananas. These ones are
这些香蕉叫什么名字，但呃，我们试试看吧。我超爱香蕉。
definitely not Caendish bananas. I am
真的，香蕉是我最喜欢的水果之一。我爱香蕉。它们有种奶油般的口感，
not sure what these bananas are called,
让人吃起来非常享受。
but uh let's try them. I do love love
love bananas. Truly, bananas are one of
my favorite fruit. I love bananas. They
just have like this creaminess to them
that really makes it like enjoyable to
eat. And they especially go well in
吃。它们尤其适合
smoothies. I love putting a banana, just
做冰沙。我喜欢往我的水果冰沙里放一根香蕉，就
one, in my uh fruit smoothie, and it
一根，它能让冰沙变得
makes it like a lot thicker and
更浓稠和
creamier. Now, let's uh try the banana.
更顺滑。现在，我们试试香蕉。
I feel like the Cavendish banana is
我觉得卡文迪什香蕉更
sweeter and creamier.
甜润和顺滑。
>> That's not a Cavendish.
这不是卡文迪什香蕉。
>> Does this look like a Cavendish to you,
你觉得这像卡文迪什香蕉吗，哥们？像99%的香蕉
>> dude? Like 99% of the bananas that are
在超市里卖的都是卡文迪什？对。
sold
不像。
>> No.
在超市里卖的都是卡文迪什？对。
>> in supermarkets are Cavendish? Yeah.
这是北美的
This is a show
展示。
>> in North America.
世界的。不，我保证你
>> No, in the world. No, I guarantee you
没有一根卡文迪什香蕉会有这样的底部。
that no Cavendish will have a bottom
你知道，我不是香蕉专家，所以我
like this.
可能说错，但如果是赌博的话，我不会赌这是
>> You know, I'm not a banana expert, so I
卡文迪什香蕉。让我拍张照片。
could be wrong, but if I was a betting
实际上香蕉有数百种，甚至数千种。所以，
man, I would not bet that this is a
我非常怀疑这些是卡文迪什香蕉。
Cavendish banana. Let me take a picture.
There are literally hundreds, if not
thousands of species of uh bananas. So,
I highly doubt that these are Cavendish.
>> I know, but like I think the stat is
我知道，但我觉得这个数据
like crazy. It's like 99.9% are
简直是疯狂。大概99.9%都是
Cavendish. And the only place you can
凯文迪什。而你能买到其他品种
really buy other species is like local
的唯一地方就是当地市场
markets or you grow it yourself.
或者你自己种植。
>> I don't know. here. I imagine they have
我不知道。这里。我想他们这里
a lot of banana production here. I don't
香蕉产量很大。我不觉得是凯文迪什。
think it's a Caven dish. I could be
我可能说错了，但味道还行。味道不错。
wrong, but it's not bad. It's not bad.
它不如加拿大产的那么甜那么香浓。
It's not as sweet and as creamy
它叫小香蕉。
>> as they are in Canada.
小香蕉
>> It's called a baby banana.
或者叫手指香蕉。
>> A baby banana
看看，我告诉你们什么了？
>> or lady finger banana.
它是凯文迪什的一个品种，
>> See guys, what did I tell you?
但不是。
>> It's a variation of a caven dish,
在马来西亚它叫pisang mas。对，我
>> but it's not.
告诉他们关于达尼的事情，北美人
>> Oh, in Malaysia it's called the pisang
没人喝达尼。或者就算喝，也是
mas. Yeah, I was telling them about Dani
因为不得不喝。
and how no one in North America drinks
是啊，那东西不好喝。
Dani. Or if they do, it's cuz they have
它确实不好喝。而且我忘了提，
to.
我们还买了洗衣粉。这个
>> Yeah, it's not good stuff.
Yeah, it's not good stuff.
>> It's not. And I forgot to mention, we
It's not. And I forgot to mention, we
also bought this laundry detergent. This
is liquid laundry detergent. You can
是洗衣液。你还可以
also get uh pods, laundry pods or
购买洗衣凝珠，洗衣凝珠或
powder. It comes in powder form as well.
洗衣粉。它也有洗衣粉形态。
I prefer pods. Those are the easiest cuz
我更喜欢洗衣凝珠。那些最方便，因
you just grab one pod and you throw it
为你只需抓取一个凝珠并扔进
in with your clothes and you don't
衣物中，你就不用
worry. This one you got to like pour it
焦虑。这种需要你像
in. Sometimes measure it out. So it's
倒入。有时需要量取。所以
like one more step, but it's really not
多了一步，但真的不算什么
a big deal. But yeah, we got this as
大事。不过，是的，我们也有
well.
这个。
>> Are you going to wash some clothes?
你要洗衣服吗？
>> I have a lot of laundry from Paneang
我有很多来自Paneang的
that I need to wash. So,
衣物需要清洗。所以，
>> but how are you going to dry it? Cuz we
但你怎么晾干？因为我们
don't have a dryer.
没有烘干机。
>> That's a washer and dryer.
那是洗衣机和烘干机。
>> Oh,
哦，
>> but I will wash it there, but I'll air
但我会去那里洗，但我会
dry it outside. Let me just show you our
在外面晾干。让我先展示一下我们的
view. I am going to maybe do a full tour
景色。我可能会完整地参观一下我们的
of our apartment. If you guys want to
公寓。如果你们想看，请在评论里
see that, let me know in the comments if
告诉我。但眼下，我就先展示一下我们
you want to see that. But for now, I'll
的美丽景色。首先，
just show you our beautiful view. First,
let me put this filter on because it
我来装上这个滤镜，因为太亮了
will be too bright. Okay, so I'm going
好的，我要打开我们的阳台门，给你们展示一下这里的景色。
to open the door to our balcony and I'll
看看这个景色。
show you the view here. Look at that
那边，我们可以看到吉隆坡的五座主要塔楼。
view.
那里，毫无疑问，最著名的就是它们，
Over there, we could see the five main
百乐宫双塔。
towers of Koala Lumpur. There you have
那边还有另一座，我不确定名字。
arguably the most famous of them all,
那边还有另一座，它是世界上最高的建筑之一。
the Patronus Twin Towers. There is
所以，是的，这就是我们的景色。
another one right there. I'm not sure
告诉我你们觉得怎么样。
the name. And there's another one right
我在之前的视频里说过，我真的想要一个视野好的阳台，
there, which is one of the tallest
所以我们决定租下这个地方，因为它视野很好。
buildings in the world. So, yeah, that's
告诉我，你们觉得这个第一人称视角怎么样？
our view. Let me know what you guys
因为对于第一人称视角，
think. I said in a previous video that I
我使用这个相机，把它固定在我的胸前。
really want to have a balcony with a
这样你们就能看到我的视角。
nice view, and uh that's why we decided
这基本上就是我看到的景象。
to rent this place for the month because
告诉我，你们想不想...
it has a nice view. Let me know guys,
what do you think of the POV? Because
for the POV,
I use this camera and I mount it onto my
chest. So then you guys can see my POV.
So this is essentially what I'm looking
at. So let me know, do you guys want to
see more videos with that camera from my
使用那台相机拍摄更多视频，从我的第一人称视角出发，并用英语解释相关内容
POV and then explaining stuff in English
采用易于理解的语言输入，同时
using comprehensible input and also
清晰缓慢地讲解。如果你想要
talking clearly and slowly. If you want
更多这样的视频，请在评论区告诉我
more videos like that, let me know in
如果不是，那我就继续使用
the comments. If not, then I'll stick to
这台相机，嗯，会像这样。更像是
using this camera and uh it'll be like
利昂手持相机拍摄的样子
this. More like Leon holding the camera
或者是我手持相机进行讲解
or me holding the camera and talking
就像这样。你喜欢第一人称视角吗？
like this. Or do you like the POV? The
整个视频不必都是第一人称视角，但
whole video doesn't have to be POV, but
像超市购物或做其他事情的部分可以采用第一人称视角，因为
maybe portions like the grocery store or
有时用这个小相机拍摄更方便。告诉我你们是否喜欢，
doing something else can be POV cuz
我会在下一个视频里见到你们。如果你认真想要
sometimes it's easier to go film with
掌握英语，我已制作了一套完整的
that small camera. Let me know if you
口语模仿和发音课程，你可以按步骤学习。你将立即获得
guys liked it or not and I'll see you
超过60节视频课程的即时访问权限。每周我会添加
guys in the next video. If you're
三到五节全新的课程来保持内容更新。而且你得到的
serious about becoming fluent in
不仅仅是
English, I've built a full speaking,
shadowing, and pronunciation course you
can follow step by step. You get instant
access to over 60 video lessons right
away. And I add three to five brand new
lessons every week to keep the content
fresh. And you're not just getting
videos. You also get an exclusive Chat
视频。您还将获得专属的Chat GPT提示，帮助您掌握任何单词的发音。此外还有
GPT prompt to help you master the
步步指导的结构，让您确切知道如何练习并充分利用每节课。内部，我们
pronunciation of any word. plus a
训练发音、口音、节奏和自然说话，让您停止犹豫并开始自信地交流。
step-by-step structure to follow so you
现在，让我们看看您加入后立即获得的内容。所以我不建议
know exactly how to practice and get the
法律a came down to heat已经热了。所以这很烦躁。牛仔裤和一件连帽衫，我
most out of every lesson. Inside, we
点击了描述中的链接加入。所以这是我们的清单。卫生纸。
train pronunciation, accent, rhythm, and
您能买到的最大的柑橘类水果。
natural speaking so you stop hesitating
您上次吃香蕉是什么时候？我要把它放入购物车。
and start speaking with real confidence.
您必须记住皮肤很厚。
Now, here's a sneak peek at what you get
是的。我不会做饭，但让我们把香蕉加入清单。这里是一堆鱼。
the moment you join. So I wouldn't take
这几乎像食人鱼。
legal a came down to heat already so
他们会扫描这个条形码，我哦。
cranky. The jeans and one hoodie which I
clicked the link in my description to
join. So this is our list. Toilet paper.
>> The biggest citrus fruit you can buy.
The biggest citrus fruit you can buy.
>> When's the last time you even had any
When's the last time you even had any
bananas? And I'm going to place it into
my shopping cart.
>> You got to remember the skin is thick.
You got to remember the skin is thick.
>> Yeah. I won't be doing any cooking, but
Yeah. I won't be doing any cooking, but
let's add banana to the list. Are a
bunch of fish here.
>> This almost looks like a piranha.
This almost looks like a piranha.
>> They'll scan this barcode and I Oh,
They'll scan this barcode and I Oh,
eggs. You think we should buy some eggs?
鸡蛋。你觉得我们应该买些鸡蛋吗？
Here we have packaged goods and there
这里我们有包装好的商品，那边
are many shelves here and we're going to
这里有很多架子，我们要
get a liquid detergent since
买液体洗涤剂，因为
>> they're 100% compostable here.
它们在这里是100%可堆肥的。
>> So Leon just tore open this plastic
所以Leon刚撕开了这个塑料
water bottle.
饮用水瓶。
>> I don't even know what kind of pans and
我甚至不知道这里有什么样的锅具和
stuff we have here.
东西。
>> I guess because people were stocking up
我想是因为人们都在囤货
on different they really do not like the
购买不同的东西，他们确实不喜欢
taste of the sonnie and I agree. So they
Sonnie的味道，我同意。所以它们
are called cabin dish bananas. These
被称为船舱香蕉。这些
ones I forgot to mention, we also bought
我忘了提，我们还买了这个洗衣液，因为它有美丽的景色。并且
this laundry cuz it has a nice view. And
如果你想买这些T恤，可以查看voca English.com。并且记住，各位，
if you want to get these t-shirts, check
你们会变得流利。
out voca English.com. And remember guys,
you will become fluent in